(this.webpackJsonplemonade=this.webpackJsonplemonade||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,,,,,,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/lucas.737e6436.svg"},,,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(28)},,,,,,,function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),s=a.n(n),r=a(6),o=a.n(r),c=a(4),i=a(3),l=a(2),u=a(1),m=a.n(u),h=(a(20),function(e){var t=e.name,a=e.onClick,n=e.className;return s.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",onClick:a,className:m()("btn",n)},t)});h.defaultProps={className:"primary-btn"};var d=h,f=a(9),w=function(e){var t=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:{};return Object(f.number_with_delimiter)(e,t)},g=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:1500;return new Promise((function(t){setTimeout((function(){t()}),e)}))},p=a(10),v=a.n(p),b=(a(21),function(e){var t=e.mode,a=e.score,n=e.onStart,r="end"===t,o=r?"Try again":"Start";return s.a.createElement("div",{className:m()("salute",{"salute-end":r})},!r&&s.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-triangle-bg"}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content-image"},s.a.createElement("img",{className:"thumb-up",src:v.a,alt:"lucas"})),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"salute-content-text"},r?s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("div",{className:"content-suptitle"},"Total score:"),s.a.createElement("h1",{className:"content-title"},"$",w(a),"earned")):s.a.createElement("h1",{className:"content-title"},"Who wants to be a millionaire?"),s.a.createElement(d,{name:o,onClick:n}))))}),E=(a(22),function(e){var t=e.isOpen,a=e.content,n=e.onClick;return Object(r.createPortal)(s.a.createElement("div",{className:"modal"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"modal-backdrop",onClick:function(){return n(!t)}}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"modal-content"},a)),document.getElementById("modal-root"))}),k=(a(23),function(e){var t=e.open,a=e.onClick;return s.a.createElement("div",{className:m()("toggle",{"toggle-open":t}),onClick:function(){return a(!t)}},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle-bar1"}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle-bar2"}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"toggle-bar3"}))}),C=(a(24),s.a.createElement("svg",{className:"svg-cell",width:"240",height:"40",viewBox:"0 0 240 40",fill:"none",xmlns:"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"},s.a.createElement("path",{d:"M13.4526 4.63788C15.6376 2.01596 18.8742 0.5 22.2872 0.5H217.713C221.126 0.5 224.362 2.01597 226.547 4.63788L239.349 20L226.547 35.3621C224.362 37.984 221.126 39.5 217.713 39.5H22.2872C18.8742 39.5 15.6376 37.984 13.4526 35.3621L0.650853 20L13.4526 4.63788Z",fill:"white",stroke:"#D0D0D8"}))),N=s.a.createElement("svg",{className:"svg-cell-mobile",width:"240",height:"32",viewBox:"0 0 240 32",fill:"none",xmlns:"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"},s.a.createElement("path",{d:"M13.5303 3.70404C15.6719 1.64809 18.5256 0.5 21.4944 0.5H218.506C221.474 0.5 224.328 1.64809 226.47 3.70404L239.278 16L226.47 28.296C224.328 30.3519 221.474 31.5 218.506 31.5H21.4944C18.5256 31.5 15.6719 30.3519 13.5303 28.296L0.721988 16L13.5303 3.70404Z",fill:"white",stroke:"#D0D0D8"})),O=function(e){var t=e.priseList,a=e.step,n=e.className;return s.a.createElement("div",{className:m()("prise-list",n)},t.map((function(e,t){return s.a.createElement("div",{key:e,className:m()("prise-list-item",{earned:t<a,active:t===a})},N,C,s.a.createElement("span",null,"$",w(e)))})))},q=a(12),y=(a(25),["A","B","C","D"]),S=s.a.createElement("svg",{width:"373",height:"72",viewBox:"0 0 373 72",fill:"none",xmlns:"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"},s.a.createElement("path",{d:"M22.7172 5.28344C24.8781 2.28016 28.3521 0.5 32.052 0.5H340.948C344.648 0.5 348.122 2.28016 350.283 5.28344L372.384 36L350.283 66.7166C348.122 69.7198 344.648 71.5 340.948 71.5H32.052C28.3521 71.5 24.8781 69.7198 22.7172 66.7166L0.615976 36L22.7172 5.28344Z",fill:"white",stroke:"#D0D0D8"})),j=function(e){var t=e.answers,a=void 0===t?[]:t,n=e.onSubmit,r=e.answerState,o=r.answer,c=Object(q.a)(r,["answer"]);return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-answers"},a.map((function(e,t){return s.a.createElement("div",{key:y[t],className:m()("game-answer",o===e&&c),onClick:function(){return o?null:n(e)}},S,s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-answer-content"},s.a.createElement("span",{className:"variant"},y[t]),s.a.createElement("span",{className:"text"},e)))})))},L=(a(26),function(e){var t=e.currentQuestion,a=e.answerState,r=e.priseList,o=e.step,c=e.onSubmit,l=Object(n.useState)(!1),u=Object(i.a)(l,2),m=u[0],h=u[1],d=s.a.createElement(O,{priseList:r,step:o});return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game"},s.a.createElement(k,{open:m,onClick:h}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-content"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-question"},s.a.createElement("h1",null,t.question)),s.a.createElement(j,{onSubmit:c,answerState:a,answers:t.answers})),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game-prises"},d)),m&&s.a.createElement(E,{isOpen:m,onClick:h,content:d}))}),W=a(11),M=["None","All","Else"],T={500:[{question:"Who wasn't a member of the Beatles?",corrects:["Justin Timberlake"],answers:["John Lennon","Paul McCartney","Ringo Star"]},{question:"Which website is the most popular search engine?",corrects:["Google"],answers:["DuckDuckGo","Myspace","Bing"]},{question:"What is the smallest unit of American currency?",corrects:["Penny"],answers:["Dime","Quarter","Dollar"]}],1e3:[{question:"In which sport do two teams pull at the opposite ends of a rope?",corrects:["Tug of war"],answers:["Basketball","Ice hockey","Polo"]},{question:"What is the first word in the phonetic alphabet?",corrects:["Alpha"],answers:["Apple","Armadillo","Amazon"]},{question:"In the novel 'The Lord of The Ring', Frodo, Sam and Bilbo come from which region of Middle Earth?",corrects:["The Shire"],answers:["The Green","The Borough","The City"]}],2e3:[{question:"Where does a cowboy wear chaps?",corrects:["On his legs"],answers:["On his head","On his arms","On his hands"]},{question:"Which of these means a speech in a play where a character talks to themselves rather than to other characters?",corrects:["Soliloquy"],answers:["Interlude","Revue","Chorus"]},{question:"In the 'Transformers' film franchise, who is the leader of the Decepticons?",corrects:["Megatron"],answers:["Megaphone","Megabyte","Megabus"]}],4e3:[{question:"Which of these zodiac signs is not represented by an animal with horns?",corrects:["Aquarius"],answers:["Taurus","Capricorn","Aries"]},{question:"Which is a Mexican stuffed, fried pancake?",corrects:["Taco"],answers:["Waco","Saki","Pesto"]}],8e3:[{question:"Sherpas and Gurkhas are native to which country?",corrects:["Nepal"],answers:["Morocco","Ecuador","Russia"]},{question:"Which of these words means confused language or technical terminology?",corrects:["Jargon"],answers:["Jardin","Jarhead","Jamjar"]}],16e3:[{question:"Escape' or 'Die Frying' is a tagline for which film?",corrects:["Chicken Run"],answers:["Ratatouille","Free Willy","Babe"]},{question:"Which of these is a 2003 Disney computer-animated film?",corrects:["Finding Nemo"],answers:["Discovering Lemo","Unearthing Zemo","Locating Remo"]}],32e3:[{question:"What is the name of the world\u2019s highest active volcano?",corrects:["Cotopaxi"],answers:["St Helens","Etna","Krakatoa"]},{question:"According to the Highway Code, what shape is the standard sign giving the order to 'Stop'?",corrects:["Octagon"],answers:["Pentagon","Hexagon","Heptagon"]}],64e3:[{question:"Which of these books is believed to have been inspired by the real-life experiences of the Scottish sailor Alexander Selkirk?",corrects:["Robinson Crusoe"],answers:["Moby Dick","The Count of Monte Cristo","Treasure Island"]},{question:"What was the nickname of Dr Leonard McCoy in the original series of 'Star Trek'?",corrects:["Bones"],answers:["Jaws","Head","Gums"]},{question:"Who was Brad Pitt's partner in the 1995 film 'Se7en'?",corrects:["Morgan Freeman"],answers:["Keanu Reeves","Bruce Willis","Matt Damon"]}],125e3:[{question:"The 2002 Booker Prize winner was Yan Martel's 'Life of ...'",corrects:["Pi"],answers:["Po","Pee","Pum"]},{question:"Who gave their name to a continent?",corrects:["Amerigo Vespucci"],answers:["Europa Bellini","Africo Tintorini","Asio Canelli"]}],25e4:[{question:"The young of which creature is known as a squab?",corrects:["Pigeon"],answers:["Salmon","Horse","Octopus"]},{question:"Which is a South American capital city?",corrects:["Cayenne"],answers:["Paprika","Mustard","Saffron"]}],5e5:[{question:"An insect\u2019s hard outer skeleton is made mainly of what substance?",corrects:["Chitin"],answers:["Keratin","Glycogen","Lignin"]},{question:"Which 2002 Tom Hanks film had the tagline, 'Every father is a hero to his son'?",corrects:["Road to Perdition"],answers:["Road to Zanzibar","Road to Glory","Road to Morocco"]}],1e6:[{question:"In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?",corrects:["Blackbeard"],answers:["Captain Kidd","Calico Jack","Bartholomew Roberts"]},{question:"Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?",corrects:["Volt"],answers:["Ohm","Hertz","Pascal"]},{question:"Who was the first man to travel into space twice?",corrects:["Gus Grissom"],answers:["Vladimir Titov","Michael Collins","Yuri Gagarin"]}]},D=Object(l.keys)(T),B=["start","end"],P={answer:"",wrong:!1,correct:!1,selected:!1},A=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)({}),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),a=t[0],r=t[1],o=Object(n.useState)(P),u=Object(i.a)(o,2),m=u[0],h=u[1],d=Object(n.useState)("start"),f=Object(i.a)(d,2),w=f[0],p=f[1],v=Object(n.useState)(0),E=Object(i.a)(v,2),k=E[0],C=E[1];Object(n.useEffect)((function(){if(k<D.length){var e=function(e){var t,a=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:500,n=Object(l.shuffle)(e[a])[0],s=n.answers,r=n.corrects,o=n.question,c=Object(l.shuffle)(r)[0];if(s.length<3){var i=Object(l.shuffle)(M);t=new Array(3-s.length).fill(null).map((function(e,t){return i[t]})).concat(s)}s.length>=3&&(t=Object(l.take)(Object(l.shuffle)(s),3));var u=Object(l.shuffle)([].concat(Object(W.a)(t),[c]));return{question:o,correct:c,answers:u}}(T,D[k]);r(e)}}),[k]);var N=k?D[k-1]:"0";return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,B.includes(w)&&s.a.createElement(b,{mode:w,score:N,onStart:function(){p("game"),C(0)}}),"game"===w&&s.a.createElement(L,{step:k,priseList:D,answerState:m,currentQuestion:a,onSubmit:function(e){h(Object(c.a)(Object(c.a)({},m),{},{answer:e,selected:!0}));var t=e.includes(a.correct),n=k===D.length-1;g().then((function(){t?(h((function(e){return Object(c.a)(Object(c.a)({},e),{},{selected:!1,correct:!0})})),g().then((function(){h(P),C(k+1),n&&p("end")}))):(h((function(e){return Object(c.a)(Object(c.a)({},e),{},{selected:!1,wrong:!0})})),g().then((function(){h(P),p("end")})))}))}}))};a(27);o.a.render(s.a.createElement(s.a.StrictMode,null,s.a.createElement(A,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}],[[13,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.b9a63471.chunk.js.map